cigabuy.com 2019-06-17

# Privacy Notice - CigaBuy

CigaBuy values its customers and respects their right to privacy. We are committed to protecting our users’ information and to making our users aware of our online practices regarding the privacy of their information. And we full comply with the EU’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), which apply across Europe on May 25, 2018.

By accessing this web site (the “Site”), you expressly consent and agree to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy, including our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree, then please do not use or access our Site.

**How We Collect Data From You.**

We use cookies (Essential cookies, Performance and functionality cookies, Analytics and customization cookies, Advertising cookies and social network cookies) to provide, protect, and improve our products and services, such as by personalizing content, offering and measuring advertisements, understanding user behavior, and providing a safer experience.

Visitors to CigaBuy can access the site’s home page and browse the site without disclosing any personally identifiable information. We may track information provided to us by your browser, including the web site you came from (known as the "referring URL"), the type of browser you use, the time and date of access, and other information that does not personally identify you.

CigaBuy may also collect personal information when you provide it to us, such as by requesting e-mail updates and newsletters, responding to a survey or questionnaire from us.

**What Information Do We Collect.**

**Data you provide:**  We collect the personal data you provide when you use our products and services or otherwise interact with us, such as when you create an account, [Contact Us](https://help.cigabuy.com/contact-us)…

**  Data about payments:** If you make a purchase, we collect personal data in connection with the purchase. This data includes your payment data, such as your credit or debit card number and other card information, and other account and authentication information, as well as billing, shipping, and contact details.

**  Data about use of our services and products:** When you visit our websites, we may collect data about the type of device you use, your device's unique identifier, the IP address of your device, your operating system, the type of Internet browser that you use, usage information, diagnostic information, and location information from or about the computers, phones, emails, or other devices on which you install or access our products or services.

**How the Information is Used.**

Generally speaking, we use personal data to provide, improve, and develop our products and services, to communicate with you, to offer you targeted advertisements and services, and to protect us and our customers.

CigaBuy determines and controls how to process your personal data as data controller for the following purposes:

·         1. **  Providing, improving, and developing our products and services**

We use your personal data to help us provide, improve, and develop our products and services. This may include using personal data for purposes such as complete shopping process, improving the users experiences, data analysis, research. Such processing is based on your prior express consent or our legitimate interest in offering you products and services. We encourage you to read those rules of privacy policy carefully before participating. If you no longer wish to agree above services we provide, please contact us to opt-out.

·         2.  **Communicating with you** ****

Subject to your prior express consent, we may use personal data to send you marketing communications in relation to our own products and services, communicate with you about your account or transactions, and inform you about our policies and terms. If you no longer wish to receive email communications for directly marketing purposes, you can just click “unsubscribe” to opt-out. If you no longer wish to agree above services we provide, please contact us to opt-out.

·         3.  **Offering and measuring targeted advertisements and services**

Subject to your prior express consent, we may use your personal data to personalize your experience with our products and services and on third-party websites and applications and to determine the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns. You are free to choose whether receive promotion information or not. If you no longer wish to agree above services we provide, please send e-mail to us to opt-out or choose ”unsubscribe” to opt out in those e-mails.

·         4 **. Promoting safety and security**

Subject to your prior express consent, we may use some technology measures to protect your personal data for helping verify accounts and user normal activities, as well as to promote data safety and security, such as by monitoring fraud and investigating suspicious or potentially illegal activity or violations of our terms or policies. Such processing is based on our legitimate interest in helping ensure the safety of our products and services.

**Your Rights**

We take reasonable steps to ensure that your personal data is accurate, complete, and up to date. You have the right to access, correct, or delete the personal data that we collect. You are also entitled to restrict or object, at any time, to the further processing of your personal data. You have the right to receive your personal data in a structured and standard format. You may lodge a complaint with the competent data protection authority regarding the processing of your personal data.

To protect the privacy and the security of your personal data, we may request data from you to enable us to confirm your identity and right to access such data, as well as to search for and provide you with the personal data we maintain. There are instances where applicable laws or regulatory requirements allow or require us to refuse to provide or delete some or all of the personal data that we maintain.

You may [Contact Us](https://help.cigabuy.com/contact-us) to exercise your rights. We will respond to your request in a reasonable timeframe, and in any event in less than 5 days.

Email: sales@cigabuy.com
